<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sn_aia_usecase">
  <sn_aia_usecase action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
    <sys_id>531034a671f3454495c8b8343feb86ff</sys_id>
    <sys_scope display_value="x_snc_medwc_auto_0">2c25847dc365875409e6d063e4013179</sys_scope>
    <sys_update_name>sn_aia_usecase_531034a671f3454495c8b8343feb86ff</sys_update_name>
    <acl>0b3b86377789444484cb9ce33f06e535</acl>
    <active>true</active>
    <base_plan>Step 1: Receive and Parse Claim Request.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to extract claim details from the customer's message: customer name, device serial number, caller name, claim reason, and urgency level.
- If the message contains "URGENT", "immediately", or "ASAP", ensure priority is set to Critical.
- DO NOT PROCEED if device serial number or claim reason cannot be identified. Ask the user to provide missing details.

Step 2: Lookup Records.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to look up the device from cmdb_ci_med_device using serial_number. If not found, inform user and stop.
- Look up the customer from core_company using customer name (LIKE query). If not found, create a new company record.
- Collect device sys_id and customer sys_id for claim creation.

Step 3: Create Warranty Claim Record.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to create a new warranty claim record with customer (reference sys_id), device (reference sys_id), caller_name, claim_reason, priority based on urgency, state=New (1).

Step 4: Refresh Warranty Data.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to call the "Lookup Device Warranty" flow action with device sys_id to update device warranty fields from the Medtric API.
- If the API returns no data, inform the user that warranty information could not be found and recommend ESCALATE.

Step 5: Search Warranty Policy Knowledge Base.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to search the Medtric Warranty Policies knowledge base for relevant coverage policy.
- Extract keywords from the claim reason to find applicable policy articles.
- Cite the KB article title and number in the decision reasoning.

Step 6: Analyze Coverage and Decide.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to analyze the claim:
  - Read device warranty data (warranty_expiration, short_description for tier info)
  - Compare claim_reason against warranty terms and KB findings
  - Check expiry date vs today
  - If expired OR not covered → DENY
  - If valid and covered → APPROVE
  - If ambiguous → ESCALATE

Step 7: Update Record with Decision.
- Use the Warranty Claims Agent to update the warranty claim record with agent_decision (Approve/Deny/Escalate), agent_recommendation (full reasoning trace), kb_article_cited (KB article number and title), and set state to appropriate value (3=Resolved for Approve, 4=Closed for Deny, -5=Pending for Escalate).

Step 8: Present Results.
- Display a formatted summary to the user:
  - Device: name, serial number
  - Customer: name
  - Warranty Status: Active/Expired with expiry date
  - Coverage Analysis: what is covered vs what was claimed
  - Policy Reference: KB article title and number cited
  - Decision: APPROVE / DENY / ESCALATE
  - Reasoning: step-by-step explanation
  - Next Steps: what happens next (fulfillment work order for approve, denial notice for deny, human review for escalate)
- NEVER invent warranty terms. Use only data from the API and knowledge base.</base_plan>
    <context_processing_script/>
    <description>Automate end-to-end warranty claim processing. Orchestrates the Warranty Claims Agent to extract claim details, look up devices and customers, verify warranty entitlements via Medtric API, analyze coverage against KB policy, and deliver approve/deny/escalate recommendations.</description>
    <execution_mode>copilot</execution_mode>
    <internal_name>global.x_snc_medwc_auto_0.Medtric Warranty Claims Automation</internal_name>
    <name>Medtric Warranty Claims Automation</name>
    <record_type>custom</record_type>
    <strategy>b264c470ff1022106c36ffffffffff67</strategy>
    <sys_domain>global</sys_domain>
    <team name="Warranty Claims Team">de3d9a0a2b634d3ca4405539e2357cce</team>
  </sn_aia_usecase>
</record_update>
